export const navItems = [
    { href: "#services", name: "Services" },
    { href: "#about", name: "About" },
    { href: "#faq", name: "Questions" },
    { href: "#contact", name: "Contact" },
];

export const lessonTypes = [
    { lessonType: "Online Lessons" },
    { lessonType: `Lessons at Student's Residence` },
];

export const lessonPrices = [
    [
        { length: "30 minute lessons", price: "$120" },
        { length: "45 minute lessons", price: "$180" },
        { length: "60 minute lessons", price: "$240" },
    ],
    [
        { length: "30 minute lessons", price: "$130+" },
        { length: "45 minute lessons", price: "$190+" },
        { length: "60 minute lessons", price: "$250+" },
    ],
];

export const comments = [
    [
        [
            { text: "Recommended for beginners" },
            { text: "$30 per lesson" },
            { text: "4 30 minute lessons" },
        ],
        [
            { text: "Recommended for intermediate students" },
            { text: "$45 per lesson" },
            { text: "4 45 minute lessons" },
        ],
        [
            { text: "Recommended for advanced students" },
            { text: "$60 per lesson" },
            { text: "4 60 minute lessons" },
        ],
    ],
    [
        [
            { text: "Recommended for beginners" },
            { text: "$30 per lesson plus gas fee" },
            { text: "Gas fee is determined by distance from city of Orange" },
            {
                text: "Only available in Orange County, California and surrounding areas",
            },
            { text: "4 30 minute lessons" },
        ],
        [
            { text: "Recommended for intermediate students" },
            { text: "$45 per lesson plus gas fee" },
            { text: "Gas fee is determined by distance from city of Orange" },
            {
                text: "Only available in Orange County, California and surrounding areas",
            },
            { text: "4 45 minute lessons" },
        ],
        [
            { text: "Recommended for advanced students" },
            { text: "$60 per lesson plus gas fee" },
            { text: "Gas fee is determined by distance from city of Orange" },
            {
                text: "Only available in Orange County, California and surrounding areas",
            },
            { text: "4 60 minute lessons" },
        ],
    ],
];

export const biography =
    "I am Andrew Dyquiangco. I am a piano teacher who has been teaching for the past six years. I studied at California State University Long Beach and received a Bachelor degree in Music Performance. I have taught students for the Certificate of Merit and National Guild of Musicians programs. My goal for my students is for them to discover the joys of learning and producing music in a pain free way. I hope for them to develop their own music tastes, find motivation to learn to play the music they love, and to just enjoy the world of music making.";

export const qAndAs = [
    {
        sectionName: "General",
        questions: [
            {
                question: "When are you available to teach?",
                answer: "I am available to teach weekdays from 1-8 PM PT and can do make up lessons Saturday from 10 AM-2 PM PT.",
            },
            {
                question: "What is your policy regarding COVID-19? Are you vaccinated?",
                answer: "For in person lessons, I do not require students or anybody else present at the lesson to wear a mask at this time. However, I do highly encourage the usage of masks. I will wear a mask and generally keep my distance unless if I have to demonstrate on the piano. I sanitize my hands before each student. I ask if the student or anyone else in the residence has any symptoms of COVID-19 (or other similar infectious diseases), please let me know as soon as you can and we will schedule a make up lesson. I am fully vaccinated against COVID-19 and have gotten a booster.",
            },
            {
                question: "What is your cancellation policy?",
                answer: "If a lesson time can't be honored by the student, the student can skip the lesson and receive a make up lesson if a) I'm given at least 24 hours before the time of the lesson, or b) the student is sick, has a mandatory event to attend, has a family emergency, or any other emergency if contact is made less than 24 hours of the lesson. If a cancellation is made without at least one of these requirements, the lesson can't be made up and will still be charged at the end of the month.",
            },
            {
                question: "What is a make up lesson and how does it work?",
                answer: "A make up lesson is given if a normal lesson can't be attended by either the student, given proper notification, or by me. We will pick a day and time to do the make up lesson. A make up lesson has no fee. I will rarely have to cancel a lesson and if I do, it will usually be at least two weeks in advanced; the exception is if I'm sick or have some other emergency.",
            },
            {
                question: "Are there any other costs besides tuition and gas fees(if applicable)?",
                answer: "The only other associated costs are the materials for the student. I am relatively conservative when it comes to assigning new required materials. The student will have to have their own copy of books, sheet music, and phone/tablet apps. I will try my best to give the most accessible and cheapest prices for said materials.",
            },
            {
                question: "When are you available for contact?",
                answer: "Generally I answer from 9 AM-9 PM PT every day. I prefer text or email during working hours as I may be teaching.",
            },
            {
                question: "How do you charge payments for lessons?",
                answer: "At the beginning of the month, the student and I will determine how many lessons we will do for the month; this will typically be one lesson a week. I will charge for those lessons at the end of that month. Any lessons missed for that month will still be charged at the end of the month. I take payments through Venmo, check, or cash.",
            },
        ],
    },
    {
        sectionName: "Lessons Structure",
        questions: [
            {
                question: "How often do you give lessons?",
                answer: "I give lessons once a week. If you want something that is structured differently, such as twice a week or every other week, I'm open to discuss it. I do think that once a week is the best for progression. Gas fees would change too.",
            },
            {
                question: "What can I expect to do at each lesson?",
                answer: "Usually a lesson will consist of playing and reviewing assigned pieces, assigning new pieces or new parts of one, reviewing theory homework, and assigning new homework. Sometimes an exercise like sightreading or ear training will be done.",
            },
            {
                question: "What is the general progression that I can expect from your lessons?",
                answer: "For beginners, I will assign a method book series appropriate for the student's age, if they doesn't already have one. There would be material for playing pieces, theory, and ear training. Once the student gets a feel for the basics, I will usually start the students on Classical music repertoire and move away from the assigned method book series. If they want to go through a structured program such as Certificate of Merit or National Guild auditions, this would be the point where I'd start enrolling them. Other than that, piece requests outside of Classical music repertoire would be encouraged now.",
            },
            {
                question: "What kind of music do you teach?",
                answer: "I am classically trained so I'll usually teach Classical music. However I've played pretty much the entire time I've been playing piano. So if there's a pop music tune you really want to learn, don't be afraid to ask me to teach you!",
            },
        ],
    },
    {
        sectionName: "In Person Lessons",
        questions: [
            {
                question: "Why are prices more expensive to have lessons at my residence than online?",
                answer: "The prices factor in travel expenses. Depending on how far you live and gas prices, I may have to charge more.",
            },
            {
                question: "Will I have to pay the gas fee prices again if I want you to teach multiple people at my residence?",
                answer: "No. As long as I teach them in a row, the gas fee prices will only have to be paid once. However, if I do have to drive to your residence multiple times in a week, then yes.",
            },
            {
                question: "How far can you drive for teaching?",
                answer: "I am based in the city of Orange. I can come drive as far as a ~20 mile radius from Orange. Other factors include time to travel and time of day of the lesson. If the lesson time asked is during peak rush hour and is about 20 miles, I probably can't accomodate that.",
            },
        ],
    },
    {
        sectionName: "Online Lessons",
        questions: [
            {
                question: "What platforms do you use for online lessons?",
                answer: "I typically use Zoom for lessons but I'm also familiar with FaceTime, Skype, and Discord. If you have a preferred video chat application not listed, let me know and I can try to make it work.",
            },
        ],
    },
];